export default[

    {
        id:1,
        question: "Cell wall",
        answer: "structures and protects the cell",
        options: [
            'assembles the subunits of ribosomes',
            'helps in digesting and recycling materials',
            'plays an important role in organizing dna',
            'structures and protects the cell'
        ]
    },

    {
        id:2,
        question: "Chloroplast",
        answer: "plays an important role in photosynthesis",
        options: [
            'increases the cell surface area and stores metabolic waste',
            'structures and protects the cell',
            'plays an important role in photosynthesis',
            'helps in digesting and recycling materials'
        ]
    },

    {
        id:3,
        question: "Central vacuole",
        answer: "increases the cell surface area and stores metabolic waste",
        options: [
            'assembles the subunits of ribosomes',
            'helps in digesting and recycling materials',
            'plays an important role in organizing dna',
            'structures and protects the cell'
        ]
    },

    {
        id:4,
        question: "Nucleus",
        answer: "plays an important role in organizing dna",
        options: [
            'assembles the subunits of ribosomes',
            'helps in digesting and recycling materials',
            'plays an important role in organizing dna',
            'structures and protects the cell'
        ]
    },

    {
        id:5,
        question: "Nucleolus",
        answer: "assembles the subunits of ribosomes",
        options: [
            'assembles the subunits of ribosomes',
            'helps in digesting and recycling materials',
            'plays an important role in organizing dna',
            'structures and protects the cell'
        ]
    },

    {
        id:6,
        question: "Ribosomes",
        answer: "synthesize protein",
        options: [
            'assembles the subunits of ribosomes',
            'helps in digesting and recycling materials',
            'plays an important role in organizing dna',
            'structures and protects the cell'
        ]
    },

    {
        id:7,
        question: "Rough Endoplasmic Reticulum",
        answer: "modifies new polypeptide chains and synthesizes lipids",
        options: [
            'assembles the subunits of ribosomes',
            'helps in digesting and recycling materials',
            'plays an important role in organizing dna',
            'structures and protects the cell'
        ]
    },

    {
        id:8,
        question: "Smooth Endoplasmic Reticulum",
        answer: "makes lipids, degrades fat and inactivates toxins",
        options: [
            'assembles the subunits of ribosomes',
            'helps in digesting and recycling materials',
            'plays an important role in organizing dna',
            'structures and protects the cell'
        ]
    },

    {
        id:9,
        question: "Golgi Body",
        answer: "modifies, sorts and ships lipids for the export or for insertion into the cell membrane",
        options: [
            'assembles the subunits of ribosomes',
            'helps in digesting and recycling materials',
            'plays an important role in organizing dna',
            'structures and protects the cell'
        ]
    },

    {
        id:10,
        question: "Lysome-like Vesticle",
        answer: "helps in digesting and recycling materials",
        options: [
            'assembles the subunits of ribosomes',
            'helps in digesting and recycling materials',
            'plays an important role in organizing dna',
            'structures and protects the cell'
        ]
    },

    {
        id:11,
        question: "Plasma Membrane",
        answer: "controls the substances going inside and out of the cell",
        options: [
            'assembles the subunits of ribosomes',
            'helps in digesting and recycling materials',
            'plays an important role in organizing dna',
            'structures and protects the cell'
        ]
    },

    {
        id:12,
        question: "Mitochondrion",
        answer: "helps in ATP formation",
        options: [
            'assembles the subunits of ribosomes',
            'helps in digesting and recycling materials',
            'plays an important role in organizing dna',
            'structures and protects the cell'
        ]
    },

    {
        id:13,
        question: "Cryoskeleton",
        answer: "structurally supports and gives shape to a cell",
        options: [
            'assembles the subunits of ribosomes',
            'helps in digesting and recycling materials',
            'plays an important role in organizing dna',
            'structures and protects the cell'
        ]
    },

    {
        id:14,
        question: "Microtubules",
        answer: "help in organizing and moving internal parts of the cell",
        options: [
            'assembles the subunits of ribosomes',
            'helps in digesting and recycling materials',
            'plays an important role in organizing dna',
            'structures and protects the cell'
        ]
    },

    {
        id:15,
        question: "Microfilaments",
        answer: "help in cell contraction, movements and structural support",
        options: [
            'assembles the subunits of ribosomes',
            'helps in digesting and recycling materials',
            'plays an important role in organizing dna',
            'structures and protects the cell'
        ]
    },

    {
        id:16,
        question: "Intermediate Filaments",
        answer: "help in strengthening the cell",
        options: [
            'assembles the subunits of ribosomes',
            'helps in digesting and recycling materials',
            'plays an important role in organizing dna',
            'structures and protects the cell'
        ]
    },


];



